So we improved chronic absenteeism, which
means everybody's coming to school more.
Because when you come
to school, you learn.
So that's how you.
You get this star rating.
And I just want to let you know
that the district recognizes it.
Middle school is my love,
passion, and joy.
That was where I spent most of my career.
So it's an honor for me to come
to a middle school because I know how hard
it is to accomplish
these things at a middle school.
And as your Princip just mentioned,
it has a lot to do with you
as leaders in this building.
I mean, first of all,
I'm seeing the pink today.
This is awesome.
And I know that has something to do
with some culture and climate things
in your school and coming together
and being united about things, but that's
led by you, the student leaders.
And I know that Ms. Baker, myself,
Ms. Carlson, we all were student
leaders at one point in time.
We were all sitting in your seats.
And you're the future of our community,
and you're the ones that lead things, and
you're already doing that in your school.
Because these accomplishments can't be
made without having a really good climate
and culture where people want to come
to school, where they love what they're
doing, where they have connections
with friends, where they feel like they
have a trusted adult,
and you help facilitate that.
When you see friends that are struggling,
you're the one that helps connect them
with the resources that they need.
When you see that we could do better as
a school, you're the one that is brave
and bold enough to go to your school
leader and say, hey, this is
an area we need to improve.
Those things matter.
Another big reason for this
award is your teachers.
Your teachers all worked really,
really hard, and they did not work
individually, because you can't
do this by working in isolation.
It's because they're a team.
They all believe in you,
and they all believe in what's doing
right by students every single day.
So as leaders, I'm going to ask that you
kind of lead the charge in helping your
fellow students thank a teacher,
because that doesn't happen without them.
And it's not just our teachers.
It's our bus Dr. It's our nutrition
workers, it's everybody in our office,
it's anyone who touches students
in their lives every day.
So take the time to thank them for what
they did, because I sure appreciate
it and I notice what they're doing.
So congratulations.
This is going to be your little award
to hang in the office or cafeteria
or wherever you decide to hang it.
But this is a big deal,
and especially for middle school.
Middle schools
really have to work hard to get this
status, and you did it,
so I'm super impressed.
Congratulations, you guys.